好了 Max
Okay, Max.
你会怎么形容我们的公寓?
How would you describe our apartment?
我已经枪毙了
And I've already ruled out
"比沉默的羔羊里的女性屠宰场还糟糕"这说法
"Worse than that girl-pit in Silence of the Lambs."
最起码她们那里还有清静的时候
Well, at least she had some silence once in a while.
听着 没人会租这样的破公寓
Look, no one's gonna pay money to rent this dump.
我们自己都半年没交租了
We haven't in six months.
每个威廉斯堡人都靠在"空中食宿"网站
Everyone else in Williamsburg is making money
出租破房子赚钱
renting their crappy places on Airbnb.
这全凭简介写得好
It's all how you describe it.
我们开始编吧
So let's start lying.
这主意真赞 我举双手赞成
This is a fantastic idea and I really want to do this.
第一条: "描述一下你的街区"
First question: "Describe your neighborhood."
破旧不堪 有很多老鼠
Run-down with a bunch of rats.
富有古典魅力 允许饲养宠物
Old-world charm. Pet-friendly.
"周围住着怎样的人?"
"What type of people live there?"
酒鬼 妓女和流浪汉
Junkies, whores, homeless.
演员居多
Actors.
"有热水浴缸吗?"
"Do you have a hot tub?"
有时有
Sometimes.
"健身房?"
"Gym?"
健身房"Gym"与人名"Jim"发音相同
有两个 楼上的弯男Jim
Two. Gay Jim upstairs,
还有一个对门的那个
and straight Jim across the hall
喝高了才变弯的直男Jim
who's only gay when he's drunk.
"什么时候可以入住?
"When is your space available?
随时可以 有时可以 只有一次"
Always, sometimes, one time."
就像我们的性生活一样
Oh, just like our sex lives.
我随时可以 有时无聊了也会有
Always for me, sometimes out of boredom,
而你只有一次
and one time for you.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
打工姐妹花 第四季第6集
协调&时间轴: 。沫
校对: 酱油影
翻译: 初见  Astral  morning
Earl 你猜我和Max干了什么
Earl, guess what Max and I did.
我知道你们没干什么
I know what you didn't do.
你们没打扫甜点展示柜
Clean this dessert carousel.
那块拿破仑酥皮蛋糕从拿破仑时期就一直在那儿
There's a Napoleon in here since Napoleon.
我们在"空中食宿"网张贴了招租广告
We rented our apartment on Airbnb.
你们把房子租给阿拉伯人了?
You rented to Arabs?
阿拉伯人"Arabs"和空中食宿"Airbnb"谐音
希望你们还能把房子收回
Well, good luck getting it back.
他们都有恐怖主义的倾向
They tend to be a TAD territorial.
"空中食宿"是一个给外地人
Airbnb is an agency that rents to out-of-towners
以及想密会小三的当地人租房子的网站
and I'm guessing local men cheating on their wives.
我成功了
Well, I did it.
我知道
I know.
你十八岁的时候跟哈里王子交往
When you were 18 with Prince Harry.
也可能是你编的
Or so you say.
我们收到了三份申请
We have three offers for our apartment.
怎么可能?
How?
我再说一遍
Let me rephrase that.
怎么可能!
How!
因为我们的宣传标语给力
I found the perfect sales pitch.
"来梦想泯灭之地居住吧"?
"Stay at the place where dreams die"?
"感受正宗的威廉斯堡生活"
"Have the authentic Williamsburg experience"
你是指被长得
Oh, you mean getting clumsily felt up
像"淘金热"时代的男人轻轻爱抚吗?
by a guy who looks like he came from the gold rush?
酒店谁都能住
Anyone can stay at a hotel.
但是在纽约有几个人能住在
But how often can you say you went to New York
"拥有一匹真马的布鲁克林
and stayed at a "Brooklyn Bohemian barn apartment
波西米亚风格的谷仓"里呢?
with a live-in horse"?
妞 你真棒
Girl, you are good.
现在我们选择谁来住我们家吧
So now we just have to pick who gets our apartment.
一个想逃避一切的男人
A guy looking to get away from it all.
这是自杀
That's a suicide.
说得对 我们说谎了 他也可能说谎
You're right. We lie, they lie.
想要重修旧好的夫妻
Um, a married couple looking to reconnect.
谋杀加自杀
Murder-suicide.
最后一个 女孩们的
And finally, a girls' getaway weekend
周末时尚派对
for some fashion model friends.
几个胖女孩
A couple of chubby girls looking to murder
想要谋杀冰淇淋
some pints of Ben and Jerry's.
或许还有芝士通心粉
With maybe a sui-side of mac and cheese.
大家好
Hey, everybody.
温度下降了
Yeah, the temperature be droppin'
姑娘们还是"美丽冻人"
and the bitches be nippin'.
我要来杯热巧克力
I need a hot chocolate.
我就在这儿呢 Sophie
I'm right here, Sophie.
我还在这儿呢 Earl
And I'm right here, Earl.
我明白你是无心的
I mean, I get it,
但她是我的 哥们
but bro code, man.
我有大事要宣布
Well, big news.
我要去旅行了
I'm going on a trip.
吃蘑菇还是迷幻药?
Mushrooms or acid?
我要去佛蒙特州!
I'm going to Vermont!
你要出门一段时间?
Oh, you're gonna be gone?
能让我们住在你家吗?
Would you mind letting us stay upstairs at your place?
我们要把公寓租出去
We're renting out our apartment.
你们要把那个破公寓租出去?
You're renting out that dump?
他们要在你们家拍"幸存者"吗?(一档真人秀)
Oh, are they filming Survivor at your place?
那些潘渴裁词焙蚶?
So when are these losers arriving?
她们不是潘
They're not losers.
她们只是一群小姑娘 付了钱想在我们公寓
They're just girls paying us to have a fun weekend
欢度周末
in our apartment.
真潘!
What losers!
一边吃冰淇淋 一边敲门的人来了
Now that is a hand that's scooped some ice cream.
嘿 你是Caroline吗?
Hi, are you Caroline?
天啊 她们真是模特
Oh, my god. They really are models.
嗨 我是莉莉
Hi, I'm Lily.
神啊 我变拉拉了
Oh shoot, now I'm gay.
莉莉・奥尔德里奇的莉莉吗?(超模)
Lily? As in Lily Aldridge?
我是玛莎・亨特(超模)
And I'm Martha.
亨特? 玛莎・亨特和莉莉・奥尔德里奇?
Hunt? Martha Hunt and Lily Aldridge?
Max 你知道她们是谁吗?
Max, do you know who they are?
当然知道
Sure do.
我就是为了她 才甩了她的
This one is the girl that I leave this one for.
不是 Max 她们是维密天使
No, Max, they're all Victoria's Secret models.
我们想在去伦敦之前
Yeah, we all wanted to hang out in New York
在纽约好好玩一下
before we leave for london.
我们要在那边走个秀
We're doing a fashion show there.
我曾经在商场的维密店工作过一天
I worked at the Victoria's Secret at the mall for one day.
但因为吃快餐弄脏了丁字裤而被解雇了
Got fired for eating panda express over the thongs.
她是Max 我是Caroline
This is Max. I'm Caroline.
我以前很有钱的
I used to be rich.
我就是那么一说
I just felt like I needed to say that.
这是我的朋友 佩特拉 加布里埃尔 瑞纳(都是超模)
And these are our friends, Petra, Gabriella, and Rina.
嗨
Hi.
太奇怪了 你们的名字都是哥伦布的船名吧
What are the odds you're all named after Columbus's ships.
进来吧 欢迎光临"威廉姆斯堡体验营"
Come in. Welcome to "The Williamsburg experience."
这地方比照片里看上去的大
It's bigger than it looks in the photo.
为了照片效果 我裁掉了几英寸边缘
Well, I shaved of a couple of inches for the photo.
你懂这技巧的
You know the drill.
你们为什么要住在这里?
So why the hell are you staying here?
难道是为自己美貌消失之后的生活做准备?
Is this training for when your looks run out?
快看 这厨房好可爱啊!
Oh, look. The kitchen is so cute!
提问 你们瞎成这样怎么走秀的?
Question, how do you walk the runway blind?
其实只是我们每次来 都住在同一家
It's just that we stay at the same Four Seasons
四季酒店里
all the time.
在这里 你们至少能感受到两个不同的季节
Well, you will experience at least two seasons here,
因为我们的恒温器坏了
'cause the thermostat's broken.
外面40华氏度 里面100度
It's 40 outside and 100 in here.
就像我们广告里说的那样 这就是我们的桑拿
So as advertised, this is our sauna.
我们波西米亚风格的谷仓就在门外
And our Bohemian barn's right out that door.
跟着凉气走就可以了
Just follow the temperature drop.
Max 有超模要住在我们家诶
Max, super models are staying at our apartment.
我太兴奋了 我要告诉我所有的小伙伴们
It's so exciting, I want to tell all my friends.
这事我好像已经干完了
I guess I just did.
你们见到小栗子了吧
I see you met Chestnut.
这是他的真名哦 不是昵称
That's his real mane, not extensions.
还有就像广告里说的那样 有扇迷人的天窗
Also per our ad, a charming skylight
你可以坐在满天星辰之下
in case you want to sit under the stars
享受一点宁静
and have a little peace and quiet.
嘿 大家好!
Hey, girls!
上来吧
Come up already.
我要去参加大学同学会了
I want to get to my college reunion.
你能相信吗? 已经十年了
Can you believe it's been 10 years?
哇 时间真的会撒谎啊...
Wow, time sure does lie...
我是说 飞逝啊
I mean, fly.
你们竟然和邻居说话?
You talk to your neighbors?
我以前和一个邻居说过话 结果
I talked to my neighbor once and the next thing you know,
我收到了娜奥米・沃茨的一封长信
I have this long letter from Naomi Watts
告诫我离她丈夫远点
saying, "Leave my husband alone."
我们现在已经认识5分钟了
So we've known each other like five minutes already.
我的免费胸罩呢?
Where's my free bra?
我现在穿着的这个只剩下框架了
I mean, all that's left of this one is the frames.
相信我 这里面就像在演滑稽剧一样
Trust me, it's like a burlesque show under here.
Sophie的公寓太棒了
Sophie's apartment is amazing.
感觉就像复活节兔子勾搭上了多金女
It looks like an easter bunny banged a golden girl.
那个淋雨喷头真好
That was some showerhead.
我都想和它结婚了 可惜它有主了...
I'd marry it, but it's already attached...
他老婆是墙
to the wall.
Max 你在哪?
Max?
我在这儿!
Here!
这床就像是一个
Oh, this bed is like being in the womb
没有二手烟的子宫
without all the second-hand smoke.
玛莎和莉莉都超友好
Martha and Lily were super-sweet.
能重新和名人们交朋友真的是让我太兴奋了
So exciting to be back hanging with celebrities.
是啊 也许现在你能换个新的名人故事了
Yeah and maybe now you can get a new celebrity story.
我已经听腻那个别人说你背影
I was getting really tired of hearing how someone thought
像格温妮丝・帕特洛的故事了
you were Gwyneth Paltrow from behind.
我到现在还受宠若惊呢
Still flattering.
有笑声?
Laughter?
我们的公寓里有笑声?
Coming from our apartment?
你觉得她们在笑什么?
What do you think they're laughing at?
估计是看到某张自动取款机票据上的余额了
Probably found our account balance on an ATM slip.
我打赌一定是玛莎讲了个笑话
I bet Martha said something funny.
她太有趣了
She's hilarious.
要知道 像她那么漂亮的人
You know, for someone who's so pretty,
根本不需要有个性
she never had to develop a personality.
我要去看看
I'm gonna go see.
Max 推我一下
Max, give me a shove.
就当是为以后真站悬崖边了做准备
This is good practice for the eventual cliff.
啤酒和翅膀
Beers and wings.
啤机和翅膀
派对开始了
Now it's a party.
Max 你还记得我们公寓很热的时候
Max, you know how when it gets hot down there,
我们就干坐着 大汗漓淋 拿着电风扇吹屁股吗?
we just sit, sweat, and point the fan at our junk?
她们和我们不太一样
They do it a little differently.
她们一边穿着内裤跳舞
They are dancing in their underwear,
一边喝啤酒
drinking beers.
那又怎样? 转角处的那家伙天天这么干
So? The guy on the corner does that all the time.
我被那些啤酒吸引住了
I can't take my eyes off those beers.
嘿! 你们好啊
Hey! Hi, you guys.
你们想下来喝点酒
You wanna come down, and have some beers,
凉快一会吗?
and cool off?
马上就来!
Be right down!
要是我有那些翅膀就好了 这样我就能快点飞下去了
Now I wish I had those wings, I could get down there faster.
说吧 是什么大消息啊?
Okay. So what is this big news?
是卫生检疫的人发现
Did the health inspector find out
我们的人造蟹肉其实是猫肉?
that the imitation crab meat is cat?
严格意义上来讲 是人造猫肉
Technically, it's imitation cat,
不过我们想说的不是这个
but that's not what we're announcing.
我来了
I'm here.
快点说 我正忙着呢
And make this snappy. I'm in the middle of something.
享受青春期?
Puberty?
不 我刚刚在和"Ripley信不信"节目通电话
No. I was on a call with Ripley's Believe It or Not
告诉他们你们还在这里工作
to inform them that you still work here.
但他们不信
And they didn't believe it.
好了 我们有几个朋友要来吃饭
Okay. We have some friends coming in for a meal
我不希望你们们反应过度 让我们难堪
and we don't want you guys to embarrass us and overreact.
亲爱的 我从来不会反应过度
Darlin', I don't overreact.
我是个七十多岁的老头 还有心脏病
I'm 70-something years old with a history of heart trouble.
我控制得住
I keep it in check.
嘿 Max! Caroline!
Hey, Max! Caroline!
我的心脏病药就在口袋里
And I keep my heart pills in my pocket.
我先走了 虽然我很享受这景象
Excuse me, much as I enjoy the view,
但我还想活到一百岁 听Al Roker
I really want that "100th Birthday" shout out
给我祝寿呢
from Al Roker.
是的 她们是维密的模特 还是我们的朋友
Yes, they're Victoria's Secret models and our friends.
昨晚我们一夜没睡 在说凯特・摩丝的坏话呢
Last night we all stayed up late trashing Kate Moss.
有模特来我的餐厅了!
Models in my diner!
不 我穿错毛线背心了
Oh, no. I wore the wrong sweater vest.
脸 身子和性格也都错了
You also wore the wrong face, body, and personality.
Max 我们去打个招呼吧
Max, let's go say hi.
我看上去怎么样?
How do I look?
像个女服务员
Like a waitress.
我靠 本来这就是服务员的制服 是吧?
Damn it, it's the waitress uniform, isn't it?
室友们 你们好吗?
What's up, homies?
你们好吗 室友?
What's up, homie?
我又爱上我的生活了
I love my life again.
我们认识已经一整天了
Well, it's been a whole day since we met,
我的免费胸罩呢?
so where's that free bra?
Max啊!
Max!
干嘛? 这个胸罩就要断气了
What? This one's on it's last legs.
昨晚我听它一直在咳
Last night I heard it coughing.
也可以来几条新内裤
Could also use some new underwear.
我的内裤已经精疲力尽了
Mine are running on fumes.
我刚刚给David发了短信
I just texted David.
他要来啦
He's coming.
一定会是很棒的派对
This is going to be an amazing party.
- 派对?  - 是啊
- Party?  - Yeah.
我们邀请了几个朋友
We're having some friends over.
不错
Cool.
- 是吗?  - 是啊
- Yeah?  - Yeah.
就像Max说的"不错"
And like Max said, "Cool""
天啊 淡定一点
Jeez, pull it back.
你表现得比红毯上的索菲娅・维加拉(女星)
You're acting needier than Sofia Vergara
还着急
on a red carpet.
超级粉丝
Big fan.
超级 超级粉丝
Big, big fan.
这是大厨请的
Compliments of the chef.
我的招牌菜 冰棍
My specialty, popsicles.
我发现面对着厨房 不停地用舌头
I find they taste best when sucked slowly,
慢慢地吮吸时 味道是最好的
using plenty of tongue, facing the kitchen.
我无法相信我们没有被邀请
I can't believe we're not invited
参加自己公寓的最大型派对
to the biggest party in our apartment
除了蚂蚁发现了你的糖豆那次
since those ants found your jelly beans.
呦吼!
Yoo-hoo!
你们好 我们就这么被晾在上面
Hi, so we're just up here hangin' out.
做自己的事儿
Doin' our Thang.
对不起 美女 我们吵醒你了吗?
Oh, sorry, girl. Did we wake you?
回去睡觉吧
Go back to sleep.
"回去睡觉"?
"Go back to sleep"?
为什么她觉得我们这么差劲呢?
Why does she think we're so lame?
我不知道
Um, I don't know.
可能是因为你一直在说
Maybe it's 'cause you're throwing around words
像"呦吼"和"事儿"这种话 像个带着"奇多"(零食)
like "Yoo-hoo" and "Thang," Like a mom bringing cheetos
去参加睡衣派对的老妈
down to a slumber party.
这是你的错
This is your fault.
在你像个没胸罩的流浪汉一样
They were obsessed with us until you started asking
开口要文胸以后 她们就烦我们了
for bras like some bra-less homeless person.
音乐这么吵 我们是不可能睡着的
We're never gonna sleep with all that music.
看看抽屉 Sophie一定有耳塞
Check the drawer, Sophie must have ear plugs.
她住在你楼上 一定有耳塞
I mean, she lives upstairs from you.
我找到塞子了 但我不觉得是用在耳朵上的
I found plugs, but I don't think they're for your ears.
没事的 我们只要走下楼 打个招呼
It's fine, we'll just pop downstairs and say hello.
时尚圈是我的舞台
Fashion's my scene.
知道我看见什么了吗? 价格标签
Know what I'm seeing? That price tag.
把它塞回去 我得还回去的
Oh, tuck it back in, I have to return it.
好了 记住我们的约定
Okay. Remember our deal.
我为此起床穿衣服了 你这辈子都是我的奴隶
I got up and got dressed so you're my slave for life.
妞儿 你们好
Oh, hi, girls.
我以为你们是来送希腊外卖的人
I thought you were the man with the Greek food.
哇 看来我一定得脱脱上嘴唇的毛了
Wow, I have definitely got to start waxing my upper lip more.
Sophie 你怎么没去佛蒙特州?
Sophie, why aren't you in Vermont?
我撒谎了
Oh, I lied.
我没有去佛蒙特州
I didn't go to Vermont.
因为太远了 而且我不是女同
I mean, it's far and I'm not a lesbian.
不 我是留下监视Oleg的
No, I stayed in town to spy on Oleg.
我知道你们以为我很完美
I mean, I know you girls think that I'm perfect,
但我有疑心病
but I have trust issues.
那是谁的公寓?
Well then, whose apartment is that?
我住在Jim家
I'm staying at Jim's.
直的还是弯的那个?
Straight Jim's or gay Jim's?
Sophie 你忘拿包了
Sophie, you forgot your purse.
我觉得这是我的
Oh, I think this is mine.
开个玩笑 这是你的
Just kidding, it's yours.
你们好 "盐和胡椒"(女子组合)
What's up, Salt N' Pepa?
弯的那个
Gay Jim's.
妞儿 不要告诉Oleg我在这里
Oh, girls, please don't tell Oleg that I'm here.
你知道的 我一直在跟着他
You know, I've been following him around
看看我不在的这段时间 他会做什么
to see what he would do if I was not in town.
目前为止 他表现不错
And so far, you know, he's been cool.
但你知道古语有云
But you know the old saying:
"骗我一次 你真丢脸
"Cheat on me once, shame on you.
骗我两次 就割了你的蛋蛋装罐子里"
Cheat on me twice, your balls are in a jar."
天啊! 有个男的站在我们门口
Oh, my god! There's a man standing in our doorway.
我又有看门人了
I have a doorman again.
看到一个男的没有带着搜查令 驱逐通知
Weird to see a man standing in our doorway
也没有圣经就站在我们门口
without a warrant, an eviction notice,
真是奇怪
or a Bible.
借过一下 这是我们的公寓
Excuse me, this is our apartment.
对 我们一直住在这里
Yeah, we live here all the time.
没有新闻
No biggie.
没有新闻 没有电 没有租约
No biggie, and no electricity, no lease-y.
你好 我是Caroline 这是Max
Hi, I'm Caroline. This is Max.
我们住在这里
We live here.
名单上没有
Not according to the list.
先生 听我说 我们真的住这儿 我有钥匙
Sir, look, we do live here. I have a key.
关键就是名字在单子上 但是没有你
The key is to be on the list, which you are not.
好吧 我可以证明我们住这儿
Okay, I can prove we live here.
走到窗边 踢一下散热器的侧边
Go over to the window, kick the side of radiator,
有个面板会打开
a panel will open up.
你会发现一个吸了一半的大麻烟和另一个吸了一半的大麻烟
You'll find a half-smoked joint and another half-smoked joint.
证明了...
Proving...
证明什么? 你是个可怜虫?
What? That you're a poor pot head?
这太疯狂了
This is crazy.
我无法相信我在乞求走进一个
I can't believe I'm begging to get into a place
我一直想离开的地方
I've been trying to get out of.
这是一个非常高级的派对
It's a very exclusive party.
这是间破公寓
It's a dump.
我知道的 我住在这里
I should know. I live here.
今晚简直不能更糟了
This night couldn't get any worse.
把灯关了
Turn that light off.
我正在用我的夜视镜
I'm watching the Victoria's Secret super model party
看维密超模派对
with my night vision goggles.
结果更糟了
And updating.
Oleg 你怎么进来这里的?
Oleg, how did you get in here?
你以为呢?
How do you think?
这是我女朋友的公寓
It's my girlfriend's apartment.
我闯进来的
I broke in.
没错 Oleg 这是你女朋友的公寓
Yes, Oleg, it's your girlfriend's apartment
你还黑灯坐着
where you're sitting in the dark,
用夜视镜看窗户外的模特
watching models out the window with night vision goggles.
嘿! 我穿着裤子呢!
Hey! My pants are on!
不 你没穿!
No, they are not!
不是我的错
Not my fault.
楼下有五个维密超模?
Five Victoria's Secret super models downstairs?
裤子是自己跑掉的
They took themselves off.
所以你想说什么? 你才是受害者吗?
So what are you saying? You're the victim here?
要是Sophie回来 看见你坐在这儿
What would Sophie say if she came home
她会怎么说?
and saw you sitting here?
她会说"别占着望远镜"
She'd say, "stop hogging the goggles."
Oleg 我得告诉你:
Oleg, let me just say this:
佛蒙特州比你想得要近
Vermont is closer than you think.
我不知道我们的争论跑题到哪儿了
I don't know where this argument is going,
但我要去参加超模派对
but I'm going to that damn supermodel party.
Oleg 太迟了 我要冒着极大风险提醒你
Oleg, it's late, I'm gonna lay this on the line for you.
你不是乔治・克鲁尼
You're no George Clooney.
你连乔治・科斯坦萨(喜剧角色)都不是
You're not even George Costanza.
这些床单整理得太棒了
These sheets are amazing
你不可能整理得比Sophie还好
and you are never gonna do better than Sophie.
她不仅性感 还显然没有嗅觉
She is hot and clearly has no sense of smell.
我爱Sophie
I love Sophie.
我会回家的
I'll go home.
转念一想 我不相信自己能
On second thought, I don't trust myself
经过你们公寓而不进去
to walk by your apartment.
最好把我锁在这里
Better lock me in here.
Caroline! Max! 下来! 快点!
Caroline! Max! Come down here! Hurry!
我就知道! 看见没 Max?
I knew it! See, Max?
她们在求我们去
They're begging us to come.
我又回来啦
I'm back again.
你来吗?
Are you coming?
哦 让我想想
Oh, let me think.
是去楼下参加露天酒会呢 还是这上面
Downstairs with an open bar or up here,
独自和穿着紧而不白小内内的Oleg一起呢?
alone, with Oleg in his tighty-not-that-whities?
我们要把你绑起来吗?
Should we tie you up?
不了 那会让我更性奋的
No, it'll just make me hornier.
我就知道她们会让我们参加派对!
I knew they wanted us to come to the party!
她们怎么会不愿意呢?
How could they not?
昨晚我教佩特拉怎么吃面包
Last night I taught Petra how to eat bread
而不用先把它撕成小片
without tearing it into little pieces first.
别硬闯 我以前是海豹突击队的
Don't try it. I was a Navy Seal.
你以为你很厉害吗?
You think you're tough?
我曾经在装冰箱的纸箱里住了一个月
I lived in a refrigerator box for a month.
上头什么都没有
With no top.
不是说盒子 而是我的上半身
Not the box. Me.
Max Caroline 进来!
Max, Caroline, get in here!
嘿! 瞧瞧 我们是被邀请的
Hey! See we were invited.
因为我们是头号贵宾
'cause we're "A" list.
厕所堵了 我要你修好它 拜托了
The toilet is clogged and I need you to take care of it, please.
是房屋看管人的"头号人选"罢了
"A" list as in "A" Janitor list.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
你们能打电话给前台吗?
Can one of you call the concierge?
当然 Caroline!
Sure. Caroline!
等等... 你们不会只是因为
Wait, wait, wait... you didn't just call us
厕所堵了才叫我们下来的吧?
down here 'cause the toilet's clogged, did you?
不是
No.
幸好
Okay, good.
厨房水槽也堵了
The kitchen sink is backed up, too.
厕所这边 我负责修
But, toilet, I got this.
我几乎天生就是干这个的
I was almost born in one.
不好意思 借过 借过
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
好了 大家都冷静
All right, everyone just calm down.
没必要大惊小怪
No need to overreact.
那就是我们在广告中所说的游泳池
And there's the pool we mentioned in our ad.
天啊
Oh, boy.
没错 还有漂浮者
Yup, we got some floaters.
Caroline 我需要马桶塞
Caroline, I'm gonna need the plunger
再让我失个忆
and a lobotomy.
老式马桶经常出现这种情况
This happens with vintage toilets.
算是一种古典魅力
Part of their old-world charm.
有些魅力卡在你的丝瓜筋上了
We got some charm stuck on your loofah.
嘿 各位 还记得昨晚
Hey guys, remember last night
我们是怎么咬面包
how we just bit into that bread
而不撕碎它的吗? 多么欢乐的时光
without chewing it? Good times.
我要那该死的马桶塞 我不想这样死
I need that damn plunger, I don't want to die this way.
找到了 但它被别的东西勾住了
Got it, but it's caught on something.
这是什么破公寓啊?
What kind of a dump is this?
嘿! 你想要体验威廉姆斯堡生活 这就是啦!
Hey! You wanted the Williamsburg experience, this is it!
好消息 玛莎 我把你的熨斗
Good news, Martha. I have your flat iron
恢复得和以前差不多了
looking pretty much back to normal.
真好 你留着吧
Oh, that's good. Keep it.
还有 抱歉弄脏了你的羊绒毛衣
Again, sorry about your cashmere sweaters in here.
但我们用光了纸巾的时候
But when we ran out of paper towels,
你确实大叫了句 "随便用什么 快把它堵上"
You did scream, "Just use anything, make it stop."
当然 我们会花钱把它们都干洗的
And of course, we'll pay to have them all dry cleaned.
真好心 留着它们吧
Oh, that's nice. Keep them.
好了 我们可以走了
Okay, we can leave.
我刚和我的心理治疗师讲完电话
I am off the phone with my therapist.
不言而喻 我们不会收你们
And it goes without saying, we won't charge you guys
这个周末的钱
for this weekend.
不行 给你
No way. Here.
你们拿着这张支票和我那治疗师的电话号码
You are taking this check and my therapist's phone number.
我不知道没有他你们是怎么挺过来的
I do not know how you are standing up without him.
什么? 拜托 这不算什么
What? Come on, this is nothing.
曾经一整个月 地板真的裂开 还吞了我们
One month, the floor actually opened up and swallowed us.
是 我们经历过更惨的
Yeah, we've been through worse.
你们互帮互助真是太酷了
Oh, it's really cool the way you two support each other.
对 我们是一对弹力长袜
Yup, we're a pair of support hose.
说到互助...
And speaking of support...
给你 Max
Here, Max.
不是吧!
No way!
看呐 Caroline 这是Brananza的(品牌)!
Look, Caroline, it's a Bra-nanza!
Caroline 鉴于你并不需要穿胸罩...
And, Caroline, since you don't really need to wear a bra...
给你 这间公寓也许是地狱
Here. This apartment may be hell,
但你是真天使
but you are a real angel.
我的翅膀?
Aw, my own wings?
谢谢你们
Thank you, guys.
我能问个问题吗?
Hey, can I ask you something?
只要是跟老鼠没有关系就行
As long as it doesn't have anything to do with rats.
你们怎么能不邀请我们参加派对?
How come you didn't invite us to the party?
什么? 我以为玛莎跟你们说了
What? I thought Martha did.
我以为莉莉说了
I thought Lily did.
模特时刻!
Model moment!
上菜 Caroline!
Pick-up, Caroline!
我一直都知道你会死在这里
Yup, I always knew you would die here.
上菜 Max!
Pick-up, Max!
看起来不错 Max
Looking good, Max.
你们走了以后 Caroline又回来
After you drop that, have Caroline come back here
把我锁进衣橱等Sophie回家了
and lock me in the walk-in till Sophie gets home.
Max 我刚刚意识到我们算是
Max, I just realized we're kind of the supermodels
服务生中的超模
of waitressing.
我刚刚意识到我的大胸不应该总是
And I just realized my boobs aren't always supposed to hit
垂向两边
my side.